(Bernadette:)Tough crowd.
(Howard:)I'm sorry.
(Raj:)This is very sweet. Thanks.
(Howard:)So, how you doing?
(Raj:)Better. I guess
(Raj:)the news just hit me
a lot harder than I expected.
(Bernadette:)Well, of course.
(Bernadette:)I would be devastated
if my parents split up.
(Howard:)Why? Your father barely
speaks to your mother.
(Bernadette:)Well, at least
he stuck around,
(Bernadette:)not like your dad,
who just took off.
(Howard:)As you can see, we're
here to cheer you up.
(Bernadette:)Sorry, Raj.
(Bernadette:)Do you have any sense of
what happened with your folks?
(Raj:)I think, over time, they started
to resent each other,
(Raj:)and instead of talking
about the things
(Raj:)that bothered them,
they kept it bottled up,
(Raj:)and the hate just grew.
(Bernadette:)It's a shame they spent
all that time unhappy.
(Bernadette:)But sometimes,
there's muffin
you can do about it.
(Bernadette:)You get it, right?
(Penny:)Oh, it's nice
you got him that.
(Sheldon:)Oh, this isn't
for Leonard, no.
(Sheldon:)Amy bought it for me.